Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-353
  - Scholars -Graduate Women's Network
    - Fuchs, Victor: A Note on Sex Segregation in Professional Occupations (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Leevinson, R.M.: Emory U.: "Sex Discrimination and Employment Practices: An Experiement with Unconventional Job Inquiries" (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Issues of Sex Bias and Sex Fairness in Career Interest Management (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - S. and D. Bern: Sex Biased Job Advertising (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Sex Bias and Sex Fairness in Careers, Guidelines for, Assesment of... (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Abrahams, Feldman, Nash: The Self Concept and Sex-Role Attitudes ... " (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Bacon, H; Barry, H.; Child, I.L. "A Cross-Cultural Survey of Some Sex Differences in Socialization" (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Barchas, P.; E. Cohen; A. McMahon: "An Althemative Perspective to Sex Differences in Organizational Settings" (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Baruch, Grace K. and Barnett, Rosalind "Implication and Applications ofRecent Research on Feminine Development" (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - S. Bern, Androgyny ("Pyschology Looks at Sex Roles: Where Have all the Androgynous People Gone?") (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - S. and D. Bern: Psychology of Sexism (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Brown, Barbara S.: "Women and Love: A Critical Analysis of Egalitarian Possibilities" (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Castillo, Gelia T. "The Changing Role of Women in Rural Societies: A Summary of Trends and Issues" (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Davis, Margaret; Cancian, Francesca: "The Effects of Roles, Situations, and Actions on Social Identity" (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Ehrensaft, Diane; "Sex Roles" UC Berkeley School of Soc. Welfare (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Denker, Elenor Rubin: "The Facts About U.S. Women" (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Feldman, S. Shirley and Sharon C. Nash "Baby Responsiveness as a Sex-Stereotyped Behavior" (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Feldman, S. Shirley and Sharon C. Nash "The Effect of Family Formation on Sex-Stereotypic Behavior" (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Homer, Matina: "Ability ofMen and Women to Cooperate" (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Ibanez, Richard A. Sex and the Social Order: A View of Some ofthe Sociological, Psychological, and Legal Issues ..." (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Komarovsky, Mirra: "Cultural Contradictions and Sex Roles" (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Livson, Florine B.: Sex Roles (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Maccoby and Jacklin: Psychology of Sex Differences (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Pleck, J: "Resource Guide for the Study ofMen" (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Wendy Martyna, Stanford: Pyschology of Female Dependence (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Stiehm, Judith H.; "Measuring Women's Power" (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Scott, John Finley: "The American College Sorority: Its Role in Class and Ethnic Endogamy" (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Seiden, Anne M. M.D.: "Gender Differences and Sexual and Reproductive Life" (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Sobieszek, Barbara: Univ. ofRochester: "Sociology: Rules, Roles, Relationships" (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Giarretto, Henry: "Humanistic Treatment ofFather-Daughter Incest" (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Ryaveck, L.S.: "The Nature ofFemale Sexuality: A Study From Ethological, Psychosomatic, and Psychoanalytically-Oriented Perspectives" (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Sand D Bern: Women and Work (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Aronson, Melanie "Wives, Employment, and the Husband-Wife Division ofHousehold Labor" (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Chiswick, Carmel Ullman "On Estimating Earnings Function forLDCs" (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Daniels, Arlene Kaplan: "The Place ofVolunteerism in the Lives ofWomen" (Scientific Analysis Corporation) (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Henley, Milene "Quit Rates of Women Workers" (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Himmelweit, "Domestic Labor and the Mode ofProduction" Univ. of London, Depart ofEconomics (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Hirschfield, Carolyn: SU Student: "The Brief Courtship of Rosie the Riveter: Manipulation Am. Women in WWl " (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - McDonnell, Jazmyn: 1976, Stanford "Trade Union Women in the U.S." (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Miller, Erin: SU Student: "Working Women and Monopoly Capital: Subjectivist and Materialist Analyses" (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Strober, Myra: "Women and Men in the World of Work: Present and Future" (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Strober, Myra: "Wives' Labor Force Behavior and Family Consumption Patterns" (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Wilensky, Harold L.: "Work, Careers, and Social Integration" (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Dornbusch, Dr. Sanford M: Stanford U. "To Try or Not to Try" (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Stiglitz, Charlotte: "Models in Higher Education" Data for Faculty Research Seminar 1975 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Women in Higher Education (No Title) (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Elovson, Allana Cummings "The Reported Impact of Women's Studies Courses on Student's Lives" (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - The Federal College Work-Study Program: A Status Report, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Conway, Jill "Perspectives on the History ofWomen's Ed. In U.S." (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Gonzalez, Rosalinda M. "The Chicana in Southwest Labor History, 1900-75" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Lerner, Gerda: Sarah Lawrence College: "The Lady and the Mill Girl: Changes in the Status of Women in the age of Jackson" (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Sicherman, Barbara -Review Essay (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Women in History: CCWHP Research Bulletin (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Welter, Barbara: Hunter College "The Cult ofTrue Womanhood: 1820-1860" (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Abadan-Unat, Nermin; "Implications ofMigration on Emancipation and Pseudo-Emancipation ofTurkish Women" (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Aguiar, Neuma; "Brazilian Families and Households in Different Systems ofProduction" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Arizpe, Lourdes; "Women in the Informal Labour Sector of Mexico City ...Unemployment or Voluntart Choice?" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Awosika, Keziah; "Nigerian Women in the Informal Labour Market: Planning for Effective Participation" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bledsoe. Caroline; "Kpelle Women's Status and Power" (Africa) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Burkett, Elinor C.; "In Dubious Sisterhood: The Case of Spanish Colonial South America" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bunster, Ximena; "Taking Pictures: Field Method and Visual Mode" (Peru) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cebotarev, E.A.; "Rural Women in Non-Familial Activities: Credit and Political Action in Latin America" (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Chaudhurry, Rafiquil Huda; "Married Women in Urban Occupations ofBangladesh-Some Problems and Issues" (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Kay Deau 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Nancy Chodorow 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - John Dupre 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Barrie Thome 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Carl Degler 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Jane Collier and Sylvia Yanagisako 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Nel Noddings (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Susan Moller Okin (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Ruth Hubbard 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Alison Jaggar 1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Catherine MacKinnon 1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Kay Deaux / Brenda Major (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Eleanor Maccoby misc. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - JLL: fall quarter planning (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Jing Lyman Lectures 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - JLL: Flyers & Posters, 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - ILL: Fall Series 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - ILL: Winter Quarter Planning (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - ILL: Spring quarter planning (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - BA WP (Bay Area Womens Philharmonic) (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Educational Events -Institute 88-89 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Africa Unadorned: Norma Holt photography ex. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Women and Power: Swedish Visitors (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Papers on Fundraising and Volunteers (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Associates: Health Fair (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Associartes: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Associate's Brochure (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Associate's Budget Samples (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Associate's Calender (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Events / Notices from Meetings (to discuss/suggest) (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Bon Appetite / Catering Info (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Associate's Fundraising Notes (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Associate's Solicitation Mailing (Notes and Procedures) (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Fundraising: Support Group Ploicy (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Associate's Procedures for Events (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Associate's Publicity (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Associates: Service, Rentals for Events (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Associates: New Solicitations and Referals (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Associates: "An evening with ... " (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Women at Stanford -article on Jane L. Stanford (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Fundraising: Brigitte Camochan (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Fundraising: DLR's letters (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Fundraising: Info and Gift Oppor. (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Fundraising: Events attended by us (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Fundraising: Stanford Development Office (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Fundraising: Possible Speakers (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Fundraising: Business and Professional Women (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Fundraising: Women's Networks (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - New York Group (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - LA Group 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Friends ofCROW (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Washington D.C. Group (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising: So. Cal. Dev Office (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising: Los Angeles Area (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Annenberg and Jens (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising: Medical School (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Diane Middlebrook (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Doug Abrams (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Anu Banerjee (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bollerman, Karen (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Christy (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Rachel Carlton (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Carstensen, Laura (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Colborn, Rose Mary (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Davison, Jean (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Julie Dunkel (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Elkin, Eric (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Fein, Natasha (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Corinna Haberland (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Christina Hong (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Iwamasa, Julia (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Iritini, Bonita (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Lamka, Melanie (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lee, Susan Sunhyuna (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Felicia Khoja (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Carol Lieske (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Linda / IRWG Job de scrip (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Milam, Susan (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Nixon, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Poehler, Jennifer (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Riles, Elizabeth (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Savides, Stephanie (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Shaw, Dominique (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Carrie Sims (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Singh, Smita (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Thomson, Jennifer Beth (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Tillery, Anne (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tollini, Theresa (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Charli Turner (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Wolverton, Dan (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Emilie Whitehurst (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Wood, Margarete (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - An Attributinal Approach to Moods and the Menstrual Cycle (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Unnatural Selection (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Women: Sex and Sexualtiy (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Women: Sex and Sexualtiy (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - The Medical Merry Go-Round (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - The Managed Heart: Commercialization ofHuman Feeling (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Stress, Appraisal, and Coping (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Childbearing in the 1980s (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Test-Tube Women (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Test-Tube Women (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Women and Mental Health (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Sexual Physiology (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Sex Hormones (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Advertising 1Sex Appeal in (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Stanford: A Centennial Chronology (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Professorship Brochure (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - WINSE Outside Guest Speakers (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - WINSE -Summer 2001 Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Corporate 1998-1999 (Breakfast Series) (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Benefit 4/26/1998: A Festival of Words and Music (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - 1995 SEI Applications (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - 1995 SEI Attendee -June Session -Constance Cameron (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Corporate Associates 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - CA Coucnil for Humanities -Mini-Grant Info 1998 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - IRWGlnfo (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - CROW Filing Key (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Cntr for Gender Based Medical Research -Grants and Notes (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Women's Health Research Seminars Schedules (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Development -Scholar Funding 19989 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - IRWG misc -reports (conference), memorial, etc. (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Philanthropic Letters (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - NAP Board Meeting (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - NAP 4/27/01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - NAP Binder -Spring 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - NAP Packet Materials (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fall 2000 NAP mtg (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fall 2000 NAP Budget (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - National Advisory Panel April 10, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - NAP Mtg -30 & 31 Oct 97 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - April 21, 1997 NAP Meeting (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Summary Responses (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - NAP Spring 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Binder: NAP Policy Board Annual Report (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - NAP Packet: GDF Version (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - NAP Packet: Scholar Version (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 2001 Scholars Misc (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 1997-98 Scholar Materials (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 98-99 Scholar Addresses Directory Info (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1998-99 Scholar Preps (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 2000-1 Scholar Preps (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Scholar Preparations 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Scholar Preps 2001-2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Spring 1999 NAP metting (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1997-98 Scholar Preps (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1999 IRWG 25th and Scholar emails (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Scholars 20th Anniversary Presentations (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Binders (two 1994 addresses, 1 Women and Leadership) (Box 12)
    - Annual Reports (Box 12)
    - Newsletter layout (Box 12)
  - Difficult Dialogues--Transcripts
    - Box on top contains unbound Difficult Dialogues/Aging in the 21st Century transcript (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21 st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21 st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21 st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21 st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21 st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Aging in the 21st Century (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Why Is Aging a Young Person's Issue? (Box 6)
    - Difficult Dialogues / Why Is Aging a Young Person's Issue? (Box 6)
    - Folder" The Future Costs ofHealth Care in Agin Societies..." by D. Freund/T. Smeeding (Box 6)
  - Difficult Dialogues--Program Records
    - Difficult Dialogues Atlantic Philanthropies (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Difficult Dialogues CA Wellness Fdtn (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Concept Papers (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Difficult Dialogues Doug Foster contract (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Difficult Dialogues Funding Requirements (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Difficult Dialogues Honoraria to Fellows (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Individual Contributions (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Difficult D-Koret F dtn. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - DD-NAAS contract (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - DD-5/5/2001 Reception (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Car Service (Barron Limo) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Stanford Catering & Bon Appetit (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-PostagelMailing (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Logistics: Hotel Stanford Terrace (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -IRWG Background Info. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-IRWG Stationary (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Staff Roster (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Amita's Stuff-spreadsheet backup (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -P A Sheraton (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -Conference Calls (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Difficult Dialogues Year 1 -Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Difficult Dialogues Schedule 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 Meeting Agendas (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -Difficult Dialogues Fellows Roster (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Difficult Dialogues Concept Paper (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Proposal without Budget! 1999 Version (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -Smith Richardson Foundation (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Difficult Dialogues Program: Smith Richardson Foundation (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Application wi Budget (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Difficult Dialogues Fellows: Bob Binstock (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Dennis Carter (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Carroll Estes (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Doug Foster (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Robert Friedland (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Mary Goldstein (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - James Jackson (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Ron Lee (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Hazel Marcus (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Tom Rando (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Elizabeth Roden (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Tim Smeeding (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Gwen Yeo (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Honoraria Payments (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Nov. Guest Speaker Bios (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Betty Friedan (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Judy Campisi (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-September 2000 Guest Speakers (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-James Fries (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1 -Dan Callahan (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Linda Burton (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Margi Gatz (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Patricia Hill Collins Information (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - John Cogan (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Mark McClellen (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Consensus Report Information (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - November 2000 Invited Guest/Speaker (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Will Marshall (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Difficult Dialogues Web-site Information (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Foundation Fundraising Information (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Photos (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Copy Center Bills 2000 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Flight Schedule (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Difficult Dialogues 1-Event Services and Transcription Service (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Difficult Dialogues: Letters to Participants: copies (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Difficult Dialogues May-handouts given/info at meeting time (Box 8)
    - email correspondence -May 25-26, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Infopacket "Fillers" (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Difficult Dialogues Binder-Cover and Side Labels (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - March 30 and 31-Difficult Dialogues Binder Contents (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Background Reading (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - January 12-13,2001 (articles) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - March 30-31st (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Policy Brief (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - May 25-26 (articles) (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Policy Brief, Newsletters, misc. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - articles (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Background Reading (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Articles (background reading) (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - January 12-13,2001 Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence:-05-4, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - DD2 Fund: Articles 1 of2 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - DD2 Fund: Articles 2 of2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - DD2 Fund: CA State Info. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - DD2 Fund: Foundations 1 of2 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - DD2 Fund: Foundations 2 of2 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - DD2 Fund: People to Contact (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - misc. Grant Information, etc. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Aging in the 21 st Century Consensus Report (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Tim Smeeding info. packet (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Timothy Smeeding Policy Brief (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Executive Summary (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Press Advisory (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Bob Binstock (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Carroll Estes (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Dennis Carter (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Robert Friedland (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mary Goldstein (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Ron Lee (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Hazel Marcus (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - James Jackson (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tom Rando (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Betsy Roden (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Gwen Yeo (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - John Shoven (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Tim Smeeding (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Participating Organizations (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Flyers -Students (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Invitations -Policy Makers (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Invitations -General (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Invitation -Insert 2IBios (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Kresge Auditorium (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Labor and Event Services (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Flyers -Community Folks (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Meeting 2 -4 PM (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - May 5th Meeting 9-11AM (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - May 5th Reception 4-6 PM (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Program Cor. Job Description (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Thursday 1116/2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Difficult Dialogues Year 2 Program (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Data ProfileslNational Academy on Aging (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Issue Brief: Social Security Reform (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Social Security Articles (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Health Literacy Article (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Difficult Dialogues Year 2 Possible Participant List (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - The Personal Security Account 2000 Plan (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Work and Retirement Among the Black Elderly (Article) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Govemer Bush's Individual Account Proposal: Implications for Retirement Benefits (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - miscellaneous/articles (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Various Articles/ Essays (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - DD2-Car Service (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - DD2 November 2003 Meeting (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - DD2 Detailed Roster (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - DD2 -2/20-2/2112004 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Difficult Dialogue Press Information (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - DD2 Correspondence-Oct. 2002 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - DD2 Correspondence-SummerIFa1l2002 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Difficult Dialogues 2002 Planning (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Panelist: Stephanie Coontz DD2002 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - DD2002 Readings (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Difficult Dialogue 2-01/02 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - DD2-May 2002 Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - DD2 Press Materials (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - DD2 Logistics (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - DD2 Labels (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - DD2 Roster (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - DD2 Bios (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - DD2 Concept Paper (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - DDI Concept Paper (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - DD2 Agenda -Schedule (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - DD2 Planning Meeting (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - DD2 Fellows (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Banks, Richard (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Stephanie Coontz (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Foster, Douglas (moderator) (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Furstenberg, Frank (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Giudice, Linda (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Maccoby, Eleanor E. (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Padilla, Amado (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Pollack, William (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Pridmore-Brown, Michelle (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Rothblum, Esther (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Judith Stacey (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Strober, Myra (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Tsai, Jeanne (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Yanagisako, Sylvia (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Invited Guests (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Difficult Dialogues Consensus Report (Box 9, Folder 71)